[{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2ec"},"answer":"the positively sloped lines indicate when shifts start. Find 12 pm and follow the positive sloped line up to the event point(s).","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":66538,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69","time_elapsed":741140,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee305"},"answer":"To determine which events start at 12 pm, go to the x axis, and follow the lines that lean toward the right. If an event (or shift) is on that same line, then it must start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121\n121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":114012,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0","time_elapsed":885253,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee31e"},"answer":"take 12 pm spot on x-axis as the left bottom mark as a triangle which has the shift name as the top mark.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75896,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME","time_elapsed":2055459,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee337"},"answer":"there are two lines starting at certain times, the one shooting to the right will meet some lines shooting to the left, when there is an event at their intersection, that event starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":266019,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO","time_elapsed":677849,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee350"},"answer":"Look at 12pm on the time axis, and look at the line pointing diagonally to the right from 12. You will find M and L along this line, therefore they begin at 12. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":46054,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1","time_elapsed":393624,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3b4"},"answer":"I begin with looking at the Horizontal axis (Start & end time) and go up from there ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":51771,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ","time_elapsed":2841539,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3cd"},"answer":"I find 12pm on the X axis, then I take the diagonal on the right and follow it until I find dots M and L.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":83496,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035","time_elapsed":19949428,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3e6"},"answer":"Start on x axis, move right until 12pm, then go up on the line segment that starts at 12pm and goes up to the right (towards M), continue until end of line. M & L both start at 12pm because they both lay on the line up and right starting at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":66393,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX","time_elapsed":400576,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3ff"},"answer":"go to 12 pm on the x axis and then move up the line towards the right till you see dots of the events","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27514,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY","time_elapsed":472809,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee418"},"answer":"On the X axis of the graph, the start of a shift is marked by the left side of a triangle formed by the 2 lines that emerge below each shift's dot on the graph","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":81749,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41","time_elapsed":1245146,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee431"},"answer":"find 12 on x axis follow diagonal line to the right","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24765,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP","time_elapsed":498170,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee44a"},"answer":"be","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":12946,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV","time_elapsed":3607558,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee463"},"answer":"1. FIND 12 PM; 2. FOLLOW THE RIGHT, DIAGONAL LINE UP; 3. THESE SHIFTS START AT 12: M, L ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221\n221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45018,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE","time_elapsed":439075,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee47c"},"answer":"You look at the x coordinate of the graph, start & and time, look for 12pm once you have located 12pm you move diagonally to the right moving upwards and search for the letters on that line when moving diagonally","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":123608,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5","time_elapsed":1270077,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee495"},"answer":"1) Find 12pm on the horizontal axis 2) look at the diagonal line that starts from the 12pm point on the horizontal axis and that goes upwards to the right 3) the lines that lay on that diagonal line are the events that start at 12pm - in this case it's M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":124831,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C","time_elapsed":815002,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ae"},"answer":"start at 12pm on the x axis, take the northeast line and identify all the points along that line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40771,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH","time_elapsed":414317,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4e0"},"answer":"I lI look at the x-axis (time of day), locate where 12 PM is and follow the diagonal line that slants to the right, locating any points along that line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":71025,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL","time_elapsed":501678,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f9"},"answer":"Find 12 pm on the x axis and then follow the diagonal line upwards and rightwards\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":41533,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F","time_elapsed":707717,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee512"},"answer":"Follow the line to the left of 12 pm and see if there are any dots on it.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":73076,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9","time_elapsed":881021,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee52b"},"answer":"you go to 12 pm and then go diagonally right the whole time ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34748,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5","time_elapsed":487740,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee544"},"answer":"YoYou look at where the 12 is on the x axis and trace the line up that is pointed more right","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":72512,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM","time_elapsed":648891,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee55d"},"answer":"First locate 12pm on the x-axis the follow the diagonal to the right of it. Any event starting at that time will be along that line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68105,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3","time_elapsed":582810,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee576"},"answer":"go to the 12 pm mark on horizontal axis, follow diagonal up towards right, any points on that line segment would be the shifts starting at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221\n221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":78860,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0","time_elapsed":685233,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee58f"},"answer":"look at 12pm on x axis and follow line going up and to the right. Everything on that line starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49342,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO","time_elapsed":511343,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a8"},"answer":"whichever line veering right starting at the 12pm point is the starting line, so anything plotted along that right leaning line starts at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75846,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP","time_elapsed":967726,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5c1"},"answer":"Follow the line up and right that, 12pm to see what shifts are there","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":136888,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM","time_elapsed":938899,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5da"},"answer":"Go to 12pm on the x-axis and go upward to the right and see what points are on that diagonal line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75844,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR","time_elapsed":987587,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5f3"},"answer":"The diagonal line from 12pm to the 8 hour duration line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":44328,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E","time_elapsed":618851,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee60c"},"answer":"To determine what events start at 12 PM you go to the x axis that says 12 PM and you look at the right and left branches it has. This tells us that M and L both start at 12 PM even though they have different shift durations ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":60457,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL","time_elapsed":656693,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee626"},"answer":"Using the right most diagonal line that starts at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34614,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0","time_elapsed":425648,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee63f"},"answer":"gp to 12pm on the bottom of the graph and then trace up until you land on a dot","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40051,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX","time_elapsed":862312,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee658"},"answer":"follow the diagonal line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":15579,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ","time_elapsed":442355,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee671"},"answer":"I pick the letter closest to 12 PM on the graph","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34947,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF","time_elapsed":647232,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee68b"},"answer":"Locate 12 PM on the X-axis, then follow the diagonal line going upward-left. All points along that line start at 12 PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":98391,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY","time_elapsed":740649,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6a4"},"answer":"LooLook at the X axis to where 12 pm is and then go up the y axis to determine which dots are marked. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49604,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF","time_elapsed":838353,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6be"},"answer":"look at the dot and subtract the hours on the left by the time on the bottom","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":23859,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT","time_elapsed":947995,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d8"},"answer":"Look at the X-axis for the dots corresponding with the time at 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30404,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P","time_elapsed":614198,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6f2"},"answer":"You can determine what event(s) start at 12pm by first looking at the times at the bottom of the chart. From there you can go upward from 12 and see what dots align.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40000,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU","time_elapsed":584711,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee70c"},"answer":"I find 12pm on the horizontal axis and then follow the line that extends from 12pm to the upper right corner of the graph. In this case, M and L start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":64935,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44","time_elapsed":983485,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee726"},"answer":"Find 12PM on the bottom axis and follow the diagonal line up and to the right, anything on that line starts at 12PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42677,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q","time_elapsed":618089,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee73f"},"answer":"Find 12 PM on the x-axis. Trace a vertical line upwards from the 12 PM on the x-axis. All the points on that line begin at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":106930,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW","time_elapsed":742363,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee759"},"answer":"Drawing a line straight up from the x axis and the given time","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36067,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74","time_elapsed":754030,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee773"},"answer":"Which events start at the line angles up to the right at the number 12 on the x-axis start at 12 pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":43344,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR","time_elapsed":557465,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee78d"},"answer":"draw a vertical line up from 12PM","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33561,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8","time_elapsed":509051,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a7"},"answer":"The shifts that line up above 12pm on the x axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45527,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ","time_elapsed":466658,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7c1"},"answer":"look at the 12 pm dash and look up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":18911,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9","time_elapsed":382976,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7db"},"answer":"To find what event(s) start at 12pm, find it on the x-axis, where time of day is located and follow the line in the diagram all the way up. You will find that M and L start at 12 but end at different times. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":105809,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5","time_elapsed":1168112,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7f5"},"answer":"At 12 pm B and F start shifts and J ends their shift.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53073,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796","time_elapsed":692483,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee80f"},"answer":"SShifts B and G start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31335,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE","time_elapsed":780054,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee85d"},"answer":"find 12 on the bottom and then climb diagonally to the right, so the shifts starting at 12 would be M and L ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42737,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC","time_elapsed":507342,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee877"},"answer":"follow the 12 pm line that goes up towards the right. any points on that line starts at 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27504,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90","time_elapsed":174531,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8ab"},"answer":"vertical dots\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":10982,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6","time_elapsed":356059,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8c5"},"answer":"I Look at the line and go up to see which aligns with the 12 pm mark","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31502,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV","time_elapsed":258626,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8df"},"answer":"Look at the x axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":8563,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R","time_elapsed":365564,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f9"},"answer":"yyou have to look at the x axis of this graph and find where 12pm is. then you follow that point up the diagonal line until you hit a letter or letters. thoes letters or letter are the shifts or shift that starts at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":81648,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY","time_elapsed":717521,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee913"},"answer":"draw a vertical line from the 12 pm point and look at which events have start points that intersect with the line. In this case, B and F.\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":84236,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ","time_elapsed":862798,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee92d"},"answer":"If the data point is line up with 12 pm on the x axis, that is when it starts","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":59515,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM","time_elapsed":613843,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee97b"},"answer":"use the graph, find 12 on the x axis and go up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33291,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8","time_elapsed":1271358,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9fd"},"answer":"loolook at 12 pm on the x axis then move in a straight line upwards until coming to a dot","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31606,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU","time_elapsed":646950,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea17"},"answer":"I look at the x axis, go to the 12pm time, and move up the graph. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":25899,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500","time_elapsed":484062,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea31"},"answer":"Shifts that start at 12pm are along the line that goes to the right starting from 12pm, meaning that M and L start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":119852,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1","time_elapsed":749430,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea4b"},"answer":"if the left line of the dot begins at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36163,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE","time_elapsed":614489,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea65"},"answer":"Look Look at the graph where it says 12p and then look at the line to the right to see which shifts start are 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":52697,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP","time_elapsed":847727,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea7f"},"answer":"You look at B and F see they are parallel points to 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31536,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3","time_elapsed":399145,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea99"},"answer":"go to 12pm on the x axis and move up vertically to see which events are on that line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32320,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H","time_elapsed":594055,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeacd"},"answer":"go to 12pm on the X axis and go directly up to see which evnts are aligned ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":22760,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT","time_elapsed":269796,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb01"},"answer":"You look at 12 pm on the x axis and look at the number above it that occur along the same line on the y axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":29594,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX","time_elapsed":756589,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb1b"},"answer":"Looking for the letters on the graph that have lined up with 12pm (F and B)","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36578,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O","time_elapsed":517784,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb35"},"answer":"I ignore the diagonal lines and look straight above to see which events are along the 12pm vertical line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":28717,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE","time_elapsed":802754,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb4f"},"answer":"Whichever letters align with 12pm right above the horizontal axis (B and F in this case, based on my interpretation of the graph).","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":103063,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH","time_elapsed":2015618,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb69"},"answer":"Follow the line going up and to the right (diagonally) from the 12pm point on the x-axis. The points that fall on this line are shifts that start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":165799,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T","time_elapsed":736443,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb83"},"answer":"Look at what points match the point of 12 pm based on the X-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49499,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5","time_elapsed":584089,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb9d"},"answer":"Look at the bottom where time of day is and find 12pm. Afterwards, look up to see which dots are aligned with 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":73099,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU","time_elapsed":481224,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb7"},"answer":"Vertical axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":11916,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC","time_elapsed":1253084,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebd1"},"answer":"The left line moving up and to the right indicate the start time of shifts, so by finding the coordinating point and left line at 12pm, you can find what shifts start at that time","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":87212,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT","time_elapsed":866689,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebeb"},"answer":"Oh no i read the x axis wrong, 12pm is the vertex of the diamond part of the graph not the one before. From there you go up the y axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":55755,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP","time_elapsed":586980,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec39"},"answer":"Look Look at x axis and see which letter starts there/ has a point","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":26096,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O","time_elapsed":656702,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec53"},"answer":"Look at the x axis (start and end time (time of day) go to 12pm on that axis scan up and you will located the two shifts that start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":87320,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK","time_elapsed":1558678,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec6d"},"answer":"12 pm on the x-axis going up are the shifts that start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":38616,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8","time_elapsed":814827,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec87"},"answer":"F & B start at 12 because the dots are aligned with 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":54264,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0","time_elapsed":1404111,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeca1"},"answer":"look at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":38117,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ","time_elapsed":754846,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecbb"},"answer":"LookI looked at X-axis and look for 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24391,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM","time_elapsed":739556,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecd5"},"answer":"look at all of the points that fall within 12pm on the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36348,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME","time_elapsed":619107,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecef"},"answer":"Go to the x-axis and find 12 PM, then follow a vertical line up and any shifts along that line start then. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":107473,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT","time_elapsed":644217,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed09"},"answer":"you can tell which event starts by looking at where the shift ends and count backwards in order to find out when it started.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":331946,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK","time_elapsed":2153231,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed23"},"answer":"The line that starts at 12 that is diagonally shooting to the right starting from the 12 point, any dots on that line start at 12. Its hard to describe how I determined it.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":88452,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K","time_elapsed":692210,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed57"},"answer":"     You check the duration of the shift and counts backwards to determine which events start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68899,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K","time_elapsed":684091,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed71"},"answer":"Draw a vertical line up from the 12PM label on the x axis, and any dots that fall on that line are events that begin at 12PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":47411,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B","time_elapsed":930712,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeda5"},"answer":"","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":8152,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7","time_elapsed":462176,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedbf"},"answer":"any dots on the line originating from 12 pm and headed towards the right","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":58816,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S","time_elapsed":891954,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedf3"},"answer":"tthe black dots above it","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":57811,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3","time_elapsed":610307,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee27"},"answer":"LooLook at the time and see if ppl are 4 hrs ahead, on time or behind 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":536066,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX","time_elapsed":1644082,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee41"},"answer":"look at the x axis and see which dots are at the 12pm mark","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42528,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q","time_elapsed":515393,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee5b"},"answer":"look at the x axis for 12pm and then go up to see what letters are plotted there.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27780,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V","time_elapsed":1228158,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee75"},"answer":"II go to the x-coordinate where it says 12PM. Anything directly above that would the shifts that start at 12PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":58985,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T","time_elapsed":1053379,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee8f"},"answer":"dots aligning the time","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":71934,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V","time_elapsed":646349,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea9"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis where it indicates the time, and anything on the line where x =  12 will indicate events starting.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":52455,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD","time_elapsed":567606,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeec3"},"answer":"To determine what events begin at 12pm. I look first at the x-axis at the number 12, then go up and left on the line to see that both M and L start their shifts at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":89910,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E","time_elapsed":1112770,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeedd"},"answer":"look look at the x axis and find 12 pm. dots directly above 12 pm start at 12.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":37043,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0","time_elapsed":687966,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef7"},"answer":"Look on the x axis for 12pm, then follow the diagonal line that goes up and to the right of the tick at 12pm. Every dot on that line represents an event that starts at 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":44275,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q","time_elapsed":312394,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef11"},"answer":"m","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":11123,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP","time_elapsed":490022,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef2b"},"answer":"Wherever the dot is placed, is what I assume the event starts.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":51501,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV","time_elapsed":554337,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef5f"},"answer":"Trace up from the 12pm mark and mark all the shifts on the line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":38367,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH","time_elapsed":618472,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef79"},"answer":"The bullet points that are directly above 12 pm are the ones that start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42572,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5","time_elapsed":560573,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef93"},"answer":"If the data point lies on the 12 pm point on the x axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":28263,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G","time_elapsed":623277,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefad"},"answer":"You find 12pm on the x-axis, and look to the line that goes to the left diagnoally, or look straight up from 12pm on the x-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":72690,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0","time_elapsed":783943,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc7"},"answer":"Well you start by locating 12 pm and then any event(s) that are found on the upwards line from it are included... So, M nad L are events that start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":55494,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW","time_elapsed":483953,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefe1"},"answer":"we look at the x-axis at 12 and if there is a dot at 12 that is the start of a shift","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33040,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH","time_elapsed":493852,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef02f"},"answer":"All points along the right diagonal line originating from the 12 PM tick mark on the horizontal axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27536,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2","time_elapsed":443846,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef049"},"answer":"GoGoGo to the x axis and find the 12 pm indicator. Go up from there and the dots that fall on that are the shifts that start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":54641,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806","time_elapsed":463390,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef063"},"answer":"Start at 12 on the x-axis and follow the positive slope to the right","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53747,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7","time_elapsed":884064,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef07d"},"answer":"Whichever dots aligns with 12pm on the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30599,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6","time_elapsed":806110,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef097"},"answer":"look at the 12pm n the x axis and then follow that all the way up. Whichever shifts overlap are the ones that start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42545,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ","time_elapsed":688446,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0b1"},"answer":"look vertically to see if there are any dots on the line, but now im starting to seee that the shifts are shown horizontally on the graph (?)","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":76694,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04","time_elapsed":753795,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0cb"},"answer":"It is determined by the x-axis and which letters sit above the 12pm time. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":88589,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL","time_elapsed":1252839,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0ff"},"answer":"you You look at the X-axis and find 12 pm. Then find whatever dot lines up vertically in that time row.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":58336,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M","time_elapsed":712487,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef119"},"answer":"The point will have a line approaching from the right. This line represents the amount of time that has passed since beginning the shift. Following this line to zero provides you with the time the shift started. Reverse engineer this process to find which events start at 12 pm (follow the line as it goes to the right).","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":107598,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM","time_elapsed":468300,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef133"},"answer":"Look at 12 pm on the x axis and draw an imaginary line up to see what dots occur at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53550,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE","time_elapsed":711405,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef167"},"answer":"Starting at the 12pm marker on the x-axis, and going up-right using the diagonal line. Going up this diagonal line, there are the shifts M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":229448,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9","time_elapsed":2040169,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef181"},"answer":"look for 12pm on the graph and see what points fall on that line/triange.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":70997,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA","time_elapsed":663959,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef19b"},"answer":"The points above 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":19845,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4","time_elapsed":653732,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1b5"},"answer":"Shifts B and F start at 12pm because that is the x axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27389,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA","time_elapsed":230498,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1cf"},"answer":"look at x axis and find 12pm, then follow straight up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":50199,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54","time_elapsed":927830,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e9"},"answer":"You can tell by reading the x-axis of the graph which would happen to be the Start and End Time of each shift stated in 1 hour intervals of the day starting at 8am all the way to 8pm\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":78722,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU","time_elapsed":1214690,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef203"},"answer":"see vertically which alphabets are above 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":28466,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA","time_elapsed":408664,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef21d"},"answer":"TO determine what shifts start at 12pm, you need to find 12pm on the X-axis and see if there are any points straight above it(you must only go straight up from the point on the axis as if you were following a perpendicular line at that point).","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":197763,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD","time_elapsed":922505,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef237"},"answer":"see vertically above 12pm ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":14670,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG","time_elapsed":337201,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef26b"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis, the bottom of the graph and look for a dot that corresponds with \"12pm\"","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36807,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R","time_elapsed":833991,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef285"},"answer":"start at the 12pm mark and move up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":13137,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS","time_elapsed":565147,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef29f"},"answer":"I look over to the x axis to determine which events start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24897,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6","time_elapsed":574887,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b9"},"answer":"Find 12pm on the x-axis, then move all the way up the diagonal line that moves up and to the right. List every dot (event) you hit on the way to the end of the line. This gives you M and L that start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":122626,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH","time_elapsed":634974,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2d3"},"answer":"look at x axis where 12pm is and look where the plots are pointed on the y axis ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":39785,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG","time_elapsed":629357,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ed"},"answer":"Look at the letters that correspond to 12 pm on the x-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":48636,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH","time_elapsed":861525,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef321"},"answer":"Every points above the 12pm sign","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":28101,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA","time_elapsed":540347,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef33b"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis and see what dots are in a line with 12 pm. that means draw a vertical line up 12 and see what dots are in that line ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36614,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8","time_elapsed":572644,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef355"},"answer":"LL.   look at the x axis for time, look at y axis for which shift","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":46520,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN","time_elapsed":318448,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef36f"},"answer":"Events that start at 12 are on the positive slope that crosses through 12 pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":38681,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3","time_elapsed":421721,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef389"},"answer":"B and F start, J ends ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42076,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L","time_elapsed":755583,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3a3"},"answer":"Begin at point marked 12 PM at the bottom, and move diagonally up and to the right. Any shift the line intersects begins at that time.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":63018,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ","time_elapsed":507339,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3bd"},"answer":"whichever dots are on the line that corresponds with 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27175,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH","time_elapsed":438398,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d7"},"answer":"I look at the x-axis and see the 12pm mark and ID all the points that fall on x = 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27422,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E","time_elapsed":501351,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3f1"},"answer":"look at the lines connecting the dots ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":25356,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3","time_elapsed":288953,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef425"},"answer":"I look at the dots that align with 12pm on the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":35655,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39","time_elapsed":666802,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef43f"},"answer":"any points along the positively increasing line that begins at (12pm, 0) started at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":124621,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6","time_elapsed":852927,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef459"},"answer":"Shifts M and L, plus Shift B and F's coffee breaks, start at 12 PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":48259,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM","time_elapsed":1029252,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef473"},"answer":"y axisy axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":11342,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ","time_elapsed":471448,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a7"},"answer":"You look at where the number 12pm is on the chart then you go up to see what letters line up with 12pm. In this case that is F and B.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":65383,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7","time_elapsed":1144775,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4c1"},"answer":"If their are dots ontop of the number 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32979,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B","time_elapsed":623292,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4db"},"answer":"shifts b and f begin","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":190001,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK","time_elapsed":1211586,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4f5"},"answer":"I would look at the x-axis and look at all the values that fall on the 12pm measurement.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24925,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF","time_elapsed":322002,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef529"},"answer":"figure out the start time of 12 pm (look at the point and see if it has points on 12 pm axis. Calculate the start time, break, and end time of each shift. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":216589,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT","time_elapsed":1769805,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef543"},"answer":"ToTo dTo To determine what event(s) start at 12 pm, you look at the bottom and look where 12 pm is. Then you go follow the line starting where 12 pm all the way to tthe top to see what event(s) start during that time.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68181,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9","time_elapsed":1167070,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef55d"},"answer":"a point that is along the axis where 12pm is means that's when the event starts.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":72631,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08","time_elapsed":721294,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5ab"},"answer":"You look at x axis too look at time then find 12pm and look up the column to see what dots are plotted along 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":50872,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL","time_elapsed":1036055,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5c5"},"answer":"F and B start at 12pm because on the x axis of the graph, it tells you that those are the start and end times and there are shifts B and F at those times. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":51095,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N","time_elapsed":624600,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5df"},"answer":"You see the mark of 12pm in the x axis and then follow the diagonal line to the right and see all of the points plotted in that line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":67572,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF","time_elapsed":526264,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f9"},"answer":"MEntally trace a straight line starting at the 12 pm point going straight up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27318,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW","time_elapsed":478207,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef613"},"answer":"You look at how long the shift is and then go to the 12 pm on the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33053,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ","time_elapsed":684230,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef62d"},"answer":"find the dots that are in line with 12pm on the x axis\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32829,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3","time_elapsed":554606,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef647"},"answer":"look at what dots are above the 12 pm tick mark","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53963,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V","time_elapsed":835081,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef661"},"answer":"ook down a the x-axis or the start and end time axis and find 12p and then move up the graph in line with 12p and see what shift starts there ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":58896,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ","time_elapsed":1315921,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef67b"},"answer":"You go to 12pm on x axis, ignore the triangular lines and go straight up. Then you will fine B and F on 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":57013,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4","time_elapsed":6660976,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef695"},"answer":"FikDFollow the line that has a positive slope from the 12pm point on the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49996,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX","time_elapsed":452799,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6e3"},"answer":"look at the x axis find the 12pm spot and look to see if any dots are on that line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":51991,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV","time_elapsed":1037756,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef717"},"answer":"Find 12 PM on the X-axis and follow the line up to the right.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42518,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO","time_elapsed":647328,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef731"},"answer":"Looking at the X axis, find 12 PM and following up in a straight line, see what dots fall on that straight line (in this case, F and B)","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68918,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D","time_elapsed":641445,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef74b"},"answer":"Choose a point that is diagonal to the x-axis of 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":83883,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM","time_elapsed":824314,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef765"},"answer":"By looking at which plot points align with 12pm on the y axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32223,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL","time_elapsed":330179,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef799"},"answer":"You would use the x-axis label, ID 12pm and see which ones fall on that point","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24246,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ","time_elapsed":513007,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7b3"},"answer":"The diagonal line on the right determines that it is the starting time so from 12 pm go up and the two points on the right leaning diagonal line are L and M","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":86180,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5","time_elapsed":500598,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e7"},"answer":"The starting point is on the left side of each number. Therefore events M and L begin at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":52520,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ","time_elapsed":834031,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef801"},"answer":"You start at the diagonal line connected to 12Pm on the horizontal axis and follow it up and to the right and whatever points that line intersects with is a shift that starts at 12 pm. It would be M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":98921,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995","time_elapsed":791895,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef81b"},"answer":"the horizontal line pointing towards the right that begins at 12pm and end at 8 hours is the line where all the shifts that begin at 12 can be found.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":66363,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E","time_elapsed":769016,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef835"},"answer":"Just look at which dots that show on the 12 pm axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":90650,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP","time_elapsed":1134603,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef84f"},"answer":"I looked at the dots that were lined up with the 12pm tick mark\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":156159,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T","time_elapsed":1076925,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef869"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis and go to 12 then go up and see which letters are on that grid \\.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42214,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424","time_elapsed":723961,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef883"},"answer":"the point where lines with a positive slope begin represent start time. If you go to 12 pm and follow the line with a positive slope you will find that M and L start at 12 pm ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":123957,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY","time_elapsed":679475,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef89d"},"answer":"Start at the 12pm mark on the x-axis and follow the diagonal line that is going up and to the right. All of the points that are on that diagonal line are events that start at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":161695,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR","time_elapsed":866350,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b7"},"answer":"find 12 pm on the graph then follow the line pointing to the right, all dots along that line start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":37437,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8","time_elapsed":567540,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8d1"},"answer":"To see if there are any spots on the top of the 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":65474,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM","time_elapsed":1227960,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8eb"},"answer":"On the x-axis, locate 12PM and follow the line up going in an upward right direction. Shifts M and L starts at 12PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":118676,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP","time_elapsed":1236779,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef905"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis and count up from 12 PM on the axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":29434,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ","time_elapsed":608728,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef91f"},"answer":"Looking at the duration and adding onto the time of the start of a shift.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":58883,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y","time_elapsed":1111307,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef939"},"answer":"The dot under the column of 12 PM determines when the event starts","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":23402,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H","time_elapsed":868984,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef953"},"answer":"x-axis, navigate to 12pm, follow the line starting from 12 and follow it diagonally up and left, line hits M and hits L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":60374,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO","time_elapsed":466061,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef96d"},"answer":"Each point represents the letters coffee break and going down the line to the left side represents start time, therefore the letters that start at 12pm are M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":140477,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU","time_elapsed":706556,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef987"},"answer":"Look at the x axis to see the time of day look at 12pm and then see which letters line up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":128633,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5","time_elapsed":991579,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9a1"},"answer":"SeeSee is the left side of a triangle starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":59323,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9","time_elapsed":825824,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9bb"},"answer":"You determine the starting of an event by looking at the x-axis, \"Start and End Time\", and looking which ones start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":100422,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ","time_elapsed":1707308,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9d5"},"answer":"B and F start work\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":14912,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH","time_elapsed":461772,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2dd"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48093,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2de"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15283,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2df"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19684,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e0"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9861,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e1"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":28342,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e2"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11082,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e3"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32911,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e4"},"answer":"AGK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":52836,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e5"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38247,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9870,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e7"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11067,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e8"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13115,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2e9"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18327,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2ea"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8748,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2eb"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13899,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2f6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30562,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2f7"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42611,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2f8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23208,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2f9"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13857,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2fa"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36218,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2fb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11258,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2fc"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25782,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2fd"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57085,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2fe"},"answer":"IEM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":69163,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee2ff"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9011,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee300"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22961,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee301"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8279,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee302"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21448,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee303"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11658,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee304"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25950,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee30f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":42324,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee310"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25644,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee311"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17536,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee312"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17241,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee313"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58627,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee314"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":33820,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee315"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37382,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee316"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47164,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee317"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37580,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee318"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13550,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee319"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11597,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee31a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7589,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee31b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11700,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee31c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11311,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee31d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20280,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee328"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15027,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee329"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10937,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee32a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16942,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee32b"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":43898,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee32c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29984,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee32d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":19683,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee32e"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24543,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee32f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57486,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee330"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20468,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee331"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10414,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee332"},"answer":"JM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10865,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee333"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17042,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee334"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18577,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee335"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7918,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee336"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15224,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee341"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":45395,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee342"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10894,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee343"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7447,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee344"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6532,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee345"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11844,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee346"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15177,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee347"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27216,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee348"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24101,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee349"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":62257,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee34a"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7380,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee34b"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8194,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee34c"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7834,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee34d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9918,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee34e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7933,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee34f"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9886,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3a5"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":41108,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3a6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":32246,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3a7"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":74534,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3a8"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":34173,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3a9"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":138748,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3aa"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12790,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3ab"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":75210,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3ac"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":186766,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3ad"},"answer":"IM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":141702,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3ae"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":39719,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3af"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":1487203,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3b0"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18025,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3b1"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17792,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3b2"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42708,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3b3"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36166,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3be"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":43203,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3bf"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14348,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10288,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c1"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10284,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c2"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18005,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9001,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c4"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":33719,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c5"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":91701,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38132,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13149,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c8"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9225,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3c9"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10726,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3ca"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19261,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3cb"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12928,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3cc"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20610,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3d7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":10702,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3d8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9557,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3d9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11701,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3da"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7379,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3db"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12658,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3dc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15912,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3dd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12797,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3de"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":36997,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22156,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3e0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10915,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3e1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22706,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3e2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10726,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3e3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12986,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3e4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10510,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3e5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13371,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":69882,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f1"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8697,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f2"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8400,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f3"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9567,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f4"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18956,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":51227,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f6"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28970,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35611,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16914,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3f9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11360,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3fa"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6219,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3fb"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9609,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3fc"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21429,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3fd"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7837,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee3fe"},"answer":"CK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19466,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee409"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":180359,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee40a"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":51100,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee40b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22193,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee40c"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16240,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee40d"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":91223,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee40e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8967,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee40f"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34994,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee410"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":84549,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee411"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39423,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee412"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":20664,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee413"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10349,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee414"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19898,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee415"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12174,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee416"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15715,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee417"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":111081,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee422"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":33085,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee423"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12635,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee424"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9167,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee425"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10596,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee426"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12323,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee427"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13256,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee428"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22109,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee429"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35597,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee42a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16753,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee42b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10071,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee42c"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5776,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee42d"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7928,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee42e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14592,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee42f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8240,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee430"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16865,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee43b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21108,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee43c"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17995,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee43d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13880,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee43e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":42128,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee43f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27688,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee440"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15115,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee441"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36526,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee442"},"answer":"IJEFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":36265,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee443"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26591,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee444"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10973,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee445"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11078,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee446"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":51304,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee447"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23990,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee448"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5633,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee449"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12984,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee454"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40139,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee455"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6807,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee456"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7734,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee457"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":5383,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee458"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30994,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee459"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":3978,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee45a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221\n221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18646,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee45b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":98059,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee45c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35178,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee45d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":26114,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee45e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7151,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee45f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4892,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee460"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12765,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee461"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7350,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee462"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16568,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee46d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":73253,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee46e"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19423,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee46f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26536,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee470"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26294,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee471"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118328,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee472"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":45060,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee473"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":78710,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee474"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":104796,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee475"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":88267,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee476"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48038,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee477"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":56731,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee478"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":30188,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee479"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50521,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee47a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24960,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee47b"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38008,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee486"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":139697,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee487"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17835,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee488"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7115,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee489"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12609,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee48a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":40317,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee48b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15631,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee48c"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":53859,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee48d"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":84632,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee48e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":55692,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee48f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19172,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee490"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22780,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee491"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16798,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee492"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28572,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee493"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13832,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee494"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24012,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee49f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26150,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10399,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11149,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8094,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12378,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7564,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34600,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44439,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":50897,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7269,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4a9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8857,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4aa"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8433,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ab"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18422,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ac"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5200,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ad"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14790,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d1"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23792,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d2"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":34480,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d3"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16676,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d4"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18497,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d5"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15653,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d6"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10119,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d7"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":79382,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d8"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25705,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4d9"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40305,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4da"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8121,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4db"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15825,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4dc"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8585,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4dd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10957,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4de"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8250,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4df"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15814,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ea"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21554,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4eb"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9139,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ec"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15765,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ed"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10268,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ee"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58097,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4ef"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":24052,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f0"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25310,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f1"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43478,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f2"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39954,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f3"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":68933,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f4"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10252,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f5"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10600,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":47820,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f7"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":75760,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee4f8"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47913,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee503"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":38688,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee504"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16352,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee505"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13493,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee506"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10228,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee507"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":47558,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee508"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8469,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee509"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32075,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee50a"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":173353,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee50b"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22490,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee50c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":20386,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee50d"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6756,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee50e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12664,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee50f"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29530,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee510"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":27937,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee511"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":6778,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee51c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44265,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee51d"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13135,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee51e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7893,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee51f"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13097,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee520"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21809,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee521"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14887,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee522"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29854,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee523"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":11,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":83411,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee524"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40991,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee525"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11864,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee526"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9755,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee527"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8972,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee528"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14076,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee529"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9542,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee52a"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12006,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee535"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":51755,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee536"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":29251,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee537"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":42721,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee538"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":30042,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee539"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18533,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee53a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10954,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee53b"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":38108,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee53c"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":85972,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee53d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41306,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee53e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12902,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee53f"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11314,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee540"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5448,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee541"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":81419,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee542"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":14480,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee543"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9254,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee54e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":60001,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee54f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22565,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee550"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8365,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee551"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19798,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee552"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":47071,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee553"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9476,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee554"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":71028,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee555"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47977,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee556"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29750,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee557"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9101,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee558"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10484,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee559"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8077,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee55a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19364,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee55b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8518,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee55c"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":22756,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee567"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37840,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee568"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":32139,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee569"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21720,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee56a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18134,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee56b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21107,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee56c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8352,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee56d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15120,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee56e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73291,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee56f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40237,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee570"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17359,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee571"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14556,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee572"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9067,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee573"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16862,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee574"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11413,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee575"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36477,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee580"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24450,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee581"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14056,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee582"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14433,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee583"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13821,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee584"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":14406,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee585"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13442,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee586"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28034,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee587"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49893,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee588"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":58684,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee589"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18925,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee58a"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8568,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee58b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8028,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee58c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13368,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee58d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10418,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee58e"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13428,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee599"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":67865,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee59a"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8630,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee59b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10450,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee59c"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11843,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee59d"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":10838,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee59e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":35223,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee59f"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17652,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a0"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":41273,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a1"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":47160,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a2"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7063,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a3"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13059,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a4"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5785,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23235,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a6"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6377,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5a7"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16070,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b2"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":58410,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b3"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":54507,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b4"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26406,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b5"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15874,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b6"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":97776,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12585,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b8"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":111357,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5b9"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60907,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ba"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":65862,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5bb"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16116,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5bc"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15808,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5bd"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19852,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5be"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27166,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5bf"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11317,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5c0"},"answer":"AGC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":50847,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5cb"},"answer":"FKUDEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":112767,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5cc"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":46783,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5cd"},"answer":"FDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":49181,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ce"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":14,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":107202,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5cf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30680,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d0"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15936,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":54101,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d2"},"answer":"IJCOHZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":8.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":94467,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d3"},"answer":"IJE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":74915,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d4"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":53084,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d5"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17324,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13849,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d7"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15811,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12936,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5d9"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27548,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5e4"},"answer":"IO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":65726,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5e5"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11624,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5e6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":33032,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5e7"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10047,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5e8"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32055,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5e9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10962,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ea"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31181,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5eb"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":98689,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ec"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":59263,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ed"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12061,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ee"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18617,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ef"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15557,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5f0"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23719,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5f1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6763,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5f2"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10572,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5fd"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27662,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5fe"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":40245,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee5ff"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":57815,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee600"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":35767,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee601"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32402,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee602"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13151,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee603"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":45093,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee604"},"answer":"IO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39599,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee605"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31492,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee606"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23303,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee607"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":37347,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee608"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14251,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee609"},"answer":"CH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25414,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee60a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":27078,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee60b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28629,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee617"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":9246,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee618"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12668,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee619"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11769,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee61a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11328,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee61b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":6754,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee61c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9575,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee61d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25534,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee61e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":56274,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee61f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":107881,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee620"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7380,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee621"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16261,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee622"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6905,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee623"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18387,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee624"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7417,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee625"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12902,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee630"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":45381,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee631"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":52483,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee632"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":42842,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee633"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":32518,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee634"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":64694,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee635"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10286,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee636"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":94243,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee637"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73413,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee638"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":49997,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee639"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21737,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee63a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":26666,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee63b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9799,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee63c"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28089,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee63d"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7580,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee63e"},"answer":"CX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":98600,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee649"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":45183,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee64a"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13757,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee64b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14241,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee64c"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10073,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee64d"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11028,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee64e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13268,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee64f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30364,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee650"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28477,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee651"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":60210,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee652"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18140,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee653"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16962,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee654"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9562,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee655"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24099,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee656"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8240,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee657"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":43134,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee662"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37974,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee663"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28856,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee664"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16436,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee665"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":23391,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee666"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":17033,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee667"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9430,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee668"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39976,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee669"},"answer":"IEF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":118577,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee66a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":8919,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee66b"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8399,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee66c"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9482,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee66d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12055,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee66e"},"answer":"JXND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":46037,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee66f"},"answer":"IBO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10176,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee670"},"answer":"JXND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17130,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee67c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":47608,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee67d"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23469,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee67e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27612,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee67f"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20635,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee680"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":42613,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee681"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":97987,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee682"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":46635,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee683"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45749,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee684"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18267,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee685"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11026,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee686"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21945,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee687"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20284,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee688"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20221,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee689"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11817,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee68a"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18687,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee695"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20634,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee696"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11497,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee697"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16072,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee698"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":46944,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee699"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":115158,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee69a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7787,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee69b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19612,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee69c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48892,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee69d"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13218,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee69e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23710,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee69f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22441,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6a0"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18234,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6a1"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":61869,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6a2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33672,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6a3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46472,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6af"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":137973,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b0"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":233249,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b1"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":86540,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b2"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9655,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b3"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30207,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7806,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b5"},"answer":"MO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":57951,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":89897,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15432,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b8"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5936,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6b9"},"answer":"XZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":34557,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ba"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":49866,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6bb"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17742,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6bc"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9817,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6bd"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36733,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6c9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24853,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ca"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17862,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6cb"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14792,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6cc"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":32021,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6cd"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24118,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ce"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14143,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6cf"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":88685,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":27866,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d1"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24757,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d2"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":59342,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d3"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10091,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":22096,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d5"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28650,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":44412,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6d7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":6330,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6e3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25579,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6e4"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11337,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6e5"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29546,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6e6"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":38420,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6e7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58943,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6e8"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8038,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6e9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16887,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ea"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48892,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6eb"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23640,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ec"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22357,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ed"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11627,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ee"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5295,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ef"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28347,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6f0"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":45700,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6f1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37960,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6fd"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":86642,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6fe"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10227,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee6ff"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":5280,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee700"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7410,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee701"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16058,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee702"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5324,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee703"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23340,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee704"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51421,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee705"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22527,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee706"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7036,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee707"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7536,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee708"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6992,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee709"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9706,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee70a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9524,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee70b"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":8924,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee717"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36622,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee718"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24355,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee719"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32821,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee71a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":22453,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee71b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36830,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee71c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10429,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee71d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39553,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee71e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":71347,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee71f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":70455,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee720"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16313,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee721"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18323,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee722"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18541,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee723"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20502,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee724"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10141,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee725"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21431,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee730"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":59061,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee731"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":69647,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee732"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28591,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee733"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":57980,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee734"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":87621,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee735"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12830,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee736"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22316,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee737"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46675,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee738"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34844,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee739"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28570,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee73a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9576,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee73b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6231,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee73c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19626,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee73d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24923,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee73e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":40702,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee74a"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11620,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee74b"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":78765,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee74c"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":67458,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee74d"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":78291,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee74e"},"answer":"HK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27431,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee74f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11027,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee750"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25036,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee751"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":58064,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee752"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18136,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee753"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":27608,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee754"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17546,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee755"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7517,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee756"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":56204,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee757"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":38031,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee758"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":63912,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee764"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":73987,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee765"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11244,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee766"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18444,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee767"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11825,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee768"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15118,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee769"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16383,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee76a"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32776,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee76b"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50255,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee76c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":74726,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee76d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9145,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee76e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7681,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee76f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9781,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee770"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27388,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee771"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8025,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee772"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16396,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee77e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37785,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee77f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15152,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee780"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12577,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee781"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":27367,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee782"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":40226,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee783"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13053,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee784"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18203,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee785"},"answer":"IJE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":16673,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee786"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26410,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee787"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":57243,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee788"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10215,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee789"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11734,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee78a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17541,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee78b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":38119,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee78c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41496,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee798"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":54902,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee799"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7382,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee79a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10685,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee79b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":28538,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee79c"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32095,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee79d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7079,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee79e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":9352,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee79f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23264,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":10260,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28653,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5347,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3292,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a4"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":36346,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":63989,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7a6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27960,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b2"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15477,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28135,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b4"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14322,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b5"},"answer":"DB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18631,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":25692,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13858,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b8"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":1907,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7b9"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":21874,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7ba"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16890,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7bb"},"answer":"PLHZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17331,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7bc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9419,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7bd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8030,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7be"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16682,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7bf"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10982,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7c0"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25535,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7cc"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46473,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7cd"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":57048,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7ce"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18674,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7cf"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":42651,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":93152,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":34623,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d2"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":80325,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d3"},"answer":"AGK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":97494,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d4"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38567,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9682,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d6"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":31331,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10645,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d8"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33383,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7d9"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16157,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7da"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":316628,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7e6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28180,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7e7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9895,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7e8"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29892,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7e9"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":40338,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7ea"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":101069,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7eb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8670,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7ec"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":41754,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7ed"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57320,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7ee"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38954,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7ef"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":67063,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7f0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8680,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7f1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7669,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7f2"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21493,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7f3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30745,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee7f4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36087,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee800"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27376,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee801"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16461,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee802"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":49214,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee803"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":77142,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee804"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":136231,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee805"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8935,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee806"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25167,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee807"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30801,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee808"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22739,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee809"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":66614,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee80a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15116,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee80b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10322,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee80c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31979,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee80d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":50059,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee80e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44826,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee84e"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27720,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee84f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12879,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee850"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27644,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee851"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":45357,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee852"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":37973,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee853"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7261,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee854"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":56166,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee855"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45385,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee856"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19974,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee857"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18647,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee858"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18298,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee859"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17654,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee85a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11851,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee85b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9662,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee85c"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10679,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee868"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":5379,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee869"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9425,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee86a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7212,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee86b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9537,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee86c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":5301,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee86d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8945,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee86e"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16301,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee86f"},"answer":"N","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":3359,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee870"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":3543,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee871"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2867,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee872"},"answer":"N","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":2275,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee873"},"answer":"N","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":1402,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee874"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":2410,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee875"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6295,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee876"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":7250,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee89c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7700,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee89d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13312,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee89e"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14145,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee89f"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":35834,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":25095,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6018,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12929,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30639,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15645,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":26842,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10773,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3514,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":38443,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8a9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18488,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8aa"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":1301,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8b6"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23759,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8b7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15379,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8b8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20384,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8b9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12167,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8ba"},"answer":"AZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44211,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8bb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10057,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8bc"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16178,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8bd"},"answer":"OLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":8958,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8be"},"answer":"COH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":3399,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8bf"},"answer":"GC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2549,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8c0"},"answer":"CX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":2777,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8c1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":2978,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8c2"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":2597,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8c3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6054,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8c4"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":3451,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18227,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d1"},"answer":"ZHJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15084,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24117,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d3"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26657,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d4"},"answer":"FU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":23867,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5267,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29551,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32565,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d8"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16108,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8d9"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":27457,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8da"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7736,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8db"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5181,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8dc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14436,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8dd"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6917,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8de"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":1477,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8ea"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":54865,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8eb"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11158,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8ec"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18741,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8ed"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":111597,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8ee"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":77392,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8ef"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7325,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36243,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f1"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23837,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f2"},"answer":"IE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":176776,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f3"},"answer":"BO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2169,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f4"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":2633,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f5"},"answer":"FM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":2148,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f6"},"answer":"BM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":3190,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f7"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":2645,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee8f8"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":3130,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee904"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":69552,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee905"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":73147,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee906"},"answer":"ZHJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":72152,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee907"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16936,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee908"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":211931,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee909"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7241,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee90a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16262,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee90b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57702,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee90c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23926,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee90d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48041,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee90e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8807,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee90f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11373,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee910"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31459,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee911"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10827,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee912"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18302,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee91e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20403,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee91f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10754,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee920"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":85023,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee921"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8677,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee922"},"answer":"JD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":70299,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee923"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8146,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee924"},"answer":"IJFBXOZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":9,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27285,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee925"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42125,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee926"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21109,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee927"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19353,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee928"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9518,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee929"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4443,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee92a"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30278,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee92b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":28571,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee92c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":70626,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee96c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46331,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee96d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":48012,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee96e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20659,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee96f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":54002,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee970"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":93539,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee971"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7801,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee972"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14899,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee973"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42306,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee974"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19805,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee975"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":37948,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee976"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7086,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee977"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3829,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee978"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17960,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee979"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24274,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee97a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25421,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9ee"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18744,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9ef"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12998,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f0"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26686,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10473,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f2"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":84910,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6991,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":8251,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35624,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f6"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22622,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f7"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":45357,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f8"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12921,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9f9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5359,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9fa"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":74093,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9fb"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42875,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ee9fc"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":78790,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea08"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25127,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea09"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15600,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea0a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20384,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea0b"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":63879,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea0c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":105714,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea0d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10228,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea0e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":10459,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea0f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":21175,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea10"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":12909,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea11"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":31651,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea12"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6849,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea13"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5222,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea14"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13890,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea15"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15367,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea16"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27968,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea22"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":13885,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea23"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":41102,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea24"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":43222,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea25"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":65171,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea26"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":53452,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea27"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6220,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea28"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21576,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea29"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":80540,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea2a"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27542,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea2b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17148,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea2c"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10208,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea2d"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12472,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea2e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":49024,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea2f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15635,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea30"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16044,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea3c"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44230,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea3d"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26188,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea3e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14133,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea3f"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":46620,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea40"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":9652,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea41"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":32395,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea42"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":75289,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea43"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57933,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea44"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37803,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea45"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12085,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea46"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10809,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea47"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6472,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea48"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13959,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea49"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8944,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea4a"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20310,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea56"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28269,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea57"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42117,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea58"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19777,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea59"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58591,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea5a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":82214,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea5b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10524,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea5c"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":41904,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea5d"},"answer":"EFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":63023,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea5e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34097,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea5f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":70007,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea60"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13633,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea61"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7113,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea62"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":41603,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea63"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":73363,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea64"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":75311,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea70"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7941,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea71"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7539,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea72"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12493,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea73"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12823,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea74"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44035,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea75"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12209,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea76"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20181,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea77"},"answer":"IE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34568,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea78"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22398,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea79"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11120,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea7a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9013,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea7b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20266,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea7c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28167,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea7d"},"answer":"OHD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21299,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea7e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24137,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea8a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30612,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea8b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11114,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea8c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16687,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea8d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":86353,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea8e"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":72069,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea8f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6547,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea90"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19925,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea91"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37045,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea92"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26325,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea93"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":47504,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea94"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9697,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea95"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7724,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea96"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20190,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea97"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21661,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eea98"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17815,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeabe"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":4799,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeabf"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":5661,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac0"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":6618,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac1"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18483,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11077,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7710,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":7814,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":14514,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac6"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":7922,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac7"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11682,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5895,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeac9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3077,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaca"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10823,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeacb"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":37797,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeacc"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33249,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf2"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24047,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":31609,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":63842,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf5"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":78231,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":43290,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7859,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16757,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaf9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46309,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeafa"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39250,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeafb"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28209,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeafc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9948,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeafd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6042,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeafe"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":80626,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeaff"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":83580,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb00"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":84142,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb0c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32442,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb0d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15657,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb0e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14554,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb0f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16901,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb10"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":31368,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb11"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7913,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb12"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18394,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb13"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40741,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb14"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21397,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb15"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16696,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb16"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14889,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb17"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8361,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb18"},"answer":"LH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24610,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb19"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18054,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb1a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28256,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb26"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":78251,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb27"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23520,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb28"},"answer":"AO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16114,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb29"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":30823,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb2a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":222162,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb2b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11175,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb2c"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29961,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb2d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40187,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb2e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18707,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb2f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":46426,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb30"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11721,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb31"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4275,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb32"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":65114,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb33"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":35915,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb34"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38651,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb40"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":70677,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb41"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":35674,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb42"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":119039,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb43"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":243196,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb44"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":179562,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb45"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":37072,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb46"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":60394,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb47"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":129041,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb48"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":65903,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb49"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":144582,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb4a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21837,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb4b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":24296,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb4c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22176,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb4d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":80346,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb4e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":100164,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb5a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24046,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb5b"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10678,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb5c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19132,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb5d"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8549,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb5e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":75294,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb5f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9321,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb60"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15400,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb61"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":65755,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb62"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":53381,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb63"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":97152,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb64"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14493,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb65"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6468,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb66"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17471,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb67"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7092,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb68"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33572,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb74"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11937,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb75"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9646,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb76"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18900,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb77"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7414,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb78"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":26226,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb79"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":18344,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb7a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28220,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb7b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46300,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb7c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29000,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb7d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":47026,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb7e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12322,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb7f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10113,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb80"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29983,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb81"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":28358,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb82"},"answer":"GK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":85111,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb8e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19882,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb8f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18227,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb90"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8151,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb91"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10608,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb92"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":9825,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb93"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7699,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb94"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17387,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb95"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":59829,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb96"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":48503,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb97"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7091,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb98"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7395,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb99"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3883,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb9a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50399,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb9b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":25988,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeb9c"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16019,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeba8"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22353,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeba9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10371,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebaa"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":38693,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebab"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":91270,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebac"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":141905,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebad"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7245,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebae"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31816,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebaf"},"answer":"GCXOLHZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":9.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":361601,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34494,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":95039,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6716,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb3"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7097,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb4"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23097,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21509,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebb6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":206243,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc2"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":43030,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc3"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":44209,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc4"},"answer":"JB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":78697,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc5"},"answer":"DB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":33838,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44430,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10370,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc8"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18260,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebc9"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51520,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebca"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41878,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebcb"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":103757,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebcc"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14358,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebcd"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7093,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebce"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18760,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebcf"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7704,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebd0"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":26006,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebdc"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22277,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebdd"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13625,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebde"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24243,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebdf"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":37705,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36449,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7103,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16808,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":12.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":97109,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19896,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44380,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6056,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3505,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29502,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebe9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22845,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eebea"},"answer":"BM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":57936,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec2a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15264,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec2b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9017,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec2c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32381,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec2d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":31710,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec2e"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":17463,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec2f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9242,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec30"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17561,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec31"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23713,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec32"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15893,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec33"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22060,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec34"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8393,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec35"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5150,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec36"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":139716,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec37"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":47017,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec38"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":135272,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec44"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24356,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec45"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24101,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec46"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":90506,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec47"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13680,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec48"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":104877,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec49"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6779,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec4a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17270,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec4b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":124985,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec4c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":42833,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec4d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":93286,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec4e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13342,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec4f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":39584,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec50"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":160643,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec51"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":97040,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec52"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":166658,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec5e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48286,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec5f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":34691,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec60"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":35108,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec61"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":79066,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec62"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118934,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec63"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10158,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec64"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15187,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec65"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35085,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec66"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19737,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec67"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":50914,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec68"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12758,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec69"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5662,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec6a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32851,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec6b"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":70465,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec6c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":64121,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec78"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44119,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec79"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11599,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec7a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26566,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec7b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":22107,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec7c"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":87521,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec7d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":36953,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec7e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32503,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec7f"},"answer":"IJE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":157764,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec80"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22657,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec81"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23108,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec82"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12828,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec83"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":137692,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec84"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":126023,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec85"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":57293,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec86"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":262081,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec92"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48753,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec93"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13539,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec94"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16712,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec95"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":24952,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec96"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":22387,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec97"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":19334,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec98"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14261,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec99"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":99553,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec9a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":158226,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec9b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23624,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec9c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7461,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec9d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3826,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec9e"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":92224,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eec9f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23012,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeca0"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":68353,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecac"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":123912,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecad"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":72707,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecae"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":92798,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecaf"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8905,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb0"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58110,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9859,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15550,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29694,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20289,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19846,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10834,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7420,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24841,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecb9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18239,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecba"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":61328,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecc6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30340,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecc7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21421,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecc8"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23214,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecc9"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6458,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecca"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":45126,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeccb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10187,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeccc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32994,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeccd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34045,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecce"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23110,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeccf"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":136179,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecd0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9023,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecd1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6463,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecd2"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29610,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecd3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23416,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecd4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":45994,"session":"a15418907\na15418907","subject":"0LCME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16793,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22600,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece2"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16347,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":43128,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece4"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":77237,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9608,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20101,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48157,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece8"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36242,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eece9"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44767,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecea"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12600,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeceb"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10888,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecec"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23658,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeced"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24132,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecee"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28597,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecfa"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11000,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecfb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":37328,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecfc"},"answer":"AUB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":120464,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecfd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":166040,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecfe"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":109813,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eecff"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12276,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed00"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":196403,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed01"},"answer":"JMND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":219604,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed02"},"answer":"MXND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":48517,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed03"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18739,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed04"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":23694,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed05"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":25179,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed06"},"answer":"AL","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":98060,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed07"},"answer":"L","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":224894,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed08"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":72543,"session":"a16900930","subject":"NTSOK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed14"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30704,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed15"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28757,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed16"},"answer":"AZFHJKUDEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":18.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":104923,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed17"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17479,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed18"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13249,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed19"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10135,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed1a"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19137,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed1b"},"answer":"EFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":85508,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed1c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":53451,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed1d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21267,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed1e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13023,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed1f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":25153,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed20"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17012,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed21"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":19700,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed22"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":22284,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed48"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":9053,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed49"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19855,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed4a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24172,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed4b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58193,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed4c"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":20585,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed4d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11055,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed4e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24407,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed4f"},"answer":"IE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54209,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed50"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":64201,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed51"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14234,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed52"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7685,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed53"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":24280,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed54"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":158954,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed55"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15843,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed56"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":39928,"session":"a16900930","subject":"L6X0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed62"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11377,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed63"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7078,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed64"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15446,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed65"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58593,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed66"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":74212,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed67"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13368,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed68"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19578,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed69"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":66972,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed6a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40493,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed6b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":54041,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed6c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9932,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed6d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":38013,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed6e"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15072,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed6f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39606,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed70"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":63735,"session":"a16683922","subject":"KNH2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed96"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31853,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed97"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8316,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed98"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14500,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed99"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":34917,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed9a"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":50592,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed9b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13027,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed9c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31018,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed9d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55702,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed9e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17598,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eed9f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11960,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeda0"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12489,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeda1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7973,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeda2"},"answer":"JX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33610,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeda3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":19766,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeda4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":2455,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb0"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":75873,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb1"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":34561,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb2"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25756,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb3"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13475,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb4"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":141386,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9898,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb6"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36823,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54200,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35868,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedb9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28704,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedba"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14472,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedbb"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11894,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedbc"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23370,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedbd"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7412,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedbe"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":199747,"session":"a15049392","subject":"G0O8S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eede4"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44640,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eede5"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23947,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eede6"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22140,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eede7"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17628,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eede8"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":60442,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eede9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8370,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedea"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22555,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedeb"},"answer":"CX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":59111,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedec"},"answer":"IF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24207,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeded"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14524,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedee"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13217,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedef"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":33006,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedf0"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":35771,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedf1"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17653,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eedf2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24831,"session":"a15566972","subject":"Y7EP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee18"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19909,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee19"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26813,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee1a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":38523,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee1b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":148812,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee1c"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":200762,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee1d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9390,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee1e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31338,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee1f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":69617,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee20"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":75924,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee21"},"answer":"JM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":51051,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee22"},"answer":"FBXZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":74703,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee23"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":60822,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee24"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":49072,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee25"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":120155,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee26"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":53760,"session":"a15987011","subject":"776UX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee32"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24894,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee33"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16433,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee34"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21753,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee35"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":34496,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee36"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":39577,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee37"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8026,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee38"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30450,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee39"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25654,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee3a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26148,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee3b"},"answer":"BX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":52292,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee3c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7097,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee3d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5252,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee3e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17876,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee3f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":36191,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee40"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":31868,"session":"a15497274","subject":"XCK4Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee4c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28553,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee4d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16537,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee4e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":41858,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee4f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":68686,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee50"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":85633,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee51"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17653,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee52"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29916,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee53"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":61589,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee54"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":91228,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee55"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":54118,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee56"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":64934,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee57"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":132020,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee58"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":57880,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee59"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":35278,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee5a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37445,"session":"15994246","subject":"57C0V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee66"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":47780,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee67"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":98709,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee68"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":30650,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee69"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":55822,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee6a"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":67887,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee6b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12292,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee6c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37721,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee6d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60423,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee6e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26858,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee6f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":159148,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee70"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9074,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee71"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15196,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee72"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":81668,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee73"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31830,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee74"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":99708,"session":"a15534110","subject":"NV47T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee80"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22161,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee81"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21994,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee82"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12955,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee83"},"answer":"CAIOZFHJKU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":10,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":27659,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee84"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18593,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee85"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12471,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee86"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37991,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee87"},"answer":"IJM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":84970,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee88"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21392,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee89"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":88466,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee8a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10971,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee8b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5332,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee8c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":35664,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee8d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20429,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee8e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":52666,"session":"a16686754","subject":"XKX1V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee9a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22785,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee9b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8382,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee9c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13681,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee9d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":77545,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee9e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36383,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eee9f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6756,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20300,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":38847,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea2"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14136,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea3"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":42434,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10475,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8686,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea6"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":55710,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15152,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeea8"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":51818,"session":"a16138265","subject":"F4XPD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeb4"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40366,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeb5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":79536,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeb6"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21259,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeb7"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":158877,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeb8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":235834,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeb9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8582,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeba"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":79109,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeebb"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":115255,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeebc"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":45105,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeebd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10261,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeebe"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16674,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeebf"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12492,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeec0"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23502,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeec1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22166,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeec2"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37467,"session":"a15805246","subject":"CLV1E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeece"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21479,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeecf"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10930,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed0"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20304,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed1"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":57517,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed2"},"answer":"OH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":117958,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9450,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17476,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39465,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed6"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13203,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed7"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":63387,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10235,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeed9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12698,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeda"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":40134,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeedb"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":49101,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeedc"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":45974,"session":"a16364378","subject":"BYKF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeee8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":5563,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeee9"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8498,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeea"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9119,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeeb"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":5250,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeec"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":5724,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeed"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9415,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeee"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14952,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeeef"},"answer":"IJEFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":53991,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35427,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5362,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef2"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7513,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11374,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16632,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7591,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eeef6"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9822,"session":"a15769204","subject":"2NF6Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef02"},"answer":"IJD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18466,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef03"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9977,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef04"},"answer":"OK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17055,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef05"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10131,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef06"},"answer":"JD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":14684,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef07"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8305,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef08"},"answer":"AX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36519,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef09"},"answer":"KL","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":112682,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef0a"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":3879,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef0b"},"answer":"L","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2270,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef0c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10709,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef0d"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":58232,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef0e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9026,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef0f"},"answer":"IBO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9734,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef10"},"answer":"ND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15972,"session":"a17203114","subject":"OHLRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef1c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44416,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef1d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42483,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef1e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":42848,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef1f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":39141,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef20"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":26666,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef21"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16380,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef22"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39943,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef23"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32528,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef24"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30229,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef25"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7955,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef26"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12351,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef27"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11761,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef28"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27149,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef29"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11982,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef2a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19337,"session":"a17191922","subject":"K7HSV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef50"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46408,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef51"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7794,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef52"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12303,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef53"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":53918,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef54"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":51285,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef55"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12464,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef56"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18700,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef57"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30124,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef58"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36630,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef59"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":49088,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef5a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17563,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef5b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6663,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef5c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":39338,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef5d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":26909,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef5e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":42128,"session":"a16324253\na16324253","subject":"BK0TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef6a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":14688,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef6b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12773,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef6c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14199,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef6d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":45101,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef6e"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":53012,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef6f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13831,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef70"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36954,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef71"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28107,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef72"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30346,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef73"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":72391,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef74"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10337,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef75"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10761,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef76"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27220,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef77"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":26333,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef78"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41152,"session":"a17170924","subject":"SV1K5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef84"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":57217,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef85"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21588,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef86"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18582,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef87"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26419,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef88"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":103847,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef89"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9743,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef8a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21855,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef8b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":20039,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef8c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":98513,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef8d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":49648,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef8e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6802,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef8f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3665,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef90"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15600,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef91"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16141,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef92"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44132,"session":"a15449379","subject":"TE76G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef9e"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27496,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eef9f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":54919,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23036,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa1"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":14740,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa2"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44461,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":73319,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa4"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":62026,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa5"},"answer":"GC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57949,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa6"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":78704,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17163,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa8"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18984,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefa9"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9052,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefaa"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25639,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefab"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13250,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefac"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":58626,"session":"a15960978","subject":"9EYZ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefb8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36201,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefb9"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7079,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefba"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":30122,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefbb"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9992,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefbc"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24547,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefbd"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7433,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefbe"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28630,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefbf"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28242,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29424,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9920,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc2"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8223,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11209,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12304,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6330,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefc6"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13474,"session":"a16768747","subject":"0EMZW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd2"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":14798,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10429,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd4"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22827,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd5"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":49890,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd6"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":45835,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9167,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32079,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefd9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29018,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefda"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16027,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefdb"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19832,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefdc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10098,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefdd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7589,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefde"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":41726,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefdf"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30430,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6eefe0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":26020,"session":"a16122200","subject":"KEMWH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef020"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":38943,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef021"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19991,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef022"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":44792,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef023"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9645,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef024"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18069,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef025"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8605,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef026"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":13506,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef027"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34868,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef028"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35646,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef029"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7018,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef02a"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7180,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef02b"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6322,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef02c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9891,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef02d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5919,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef02e"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":6609,"session":"a159507373","subject":"TBQB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef03a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":86963,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef03b"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30452,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef03c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11257,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef03d"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":23226,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef03e"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":42929,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef03f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6837,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef040"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12688,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef041"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":15873,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef042"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13221,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef043"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15141,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef044"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7537,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef045"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4772,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef046"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10551,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef047"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21375,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef048"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27943,"session":"a17103928","subject":"MM806"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef054"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":56540,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef055"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10327,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef056"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":31694,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef057"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":128716,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef058"},"answer":"HK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":122627,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef059"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":66186,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef05a"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":47439,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef05b"},"answer":"IJEF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":8,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":82423,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef05c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":98671,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef05d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6924,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef05e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7848,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef05f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15756,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef060"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21330,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef061"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7363,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef062"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":55961,"session":"a15131176","subject":"S0WU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef06e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20696,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef06f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17758,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef070"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26230,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef071"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":95498,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef072"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":81696,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef073"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10774,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef074"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21376,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef075"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60028,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef076"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36083,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef077"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":66952,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef078"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7761,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef079"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5159,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef07a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18030,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef07b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":41253,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef07c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":58274,"session":"a16622511","subject":"Y0MZ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef088"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36623,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef089"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13367,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef08a"},"answer":"OJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":93837,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef08b"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12296,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef08c"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":51685,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef08d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":28535,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef08e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20279,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef08f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":38058,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef090"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21779,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef091"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":25565,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef092"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13241,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef093"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8124,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef094"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":83283,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef095"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":37216,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef096"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":45236,"session":"a16229507","subject":"8V8HJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a2"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":43749,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":37497,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a4"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23851,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a5"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7948,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":78630,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9050,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16393,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0a9"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":100338,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0aa"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26542,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0ab"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14138,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0ac"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8881,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0ad"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20279,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0ae"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":123367,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0af"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18345,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0b0"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23469,"session":"a17082219","subject":"X3B04"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0bc"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":110477,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0bd"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28041,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0be"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":42038,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0bf"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":22161,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c0"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":92925,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7695,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39032,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":81512,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":63603,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":111088,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14161,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":21325,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":58518,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0c9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":29544,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0ca"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":224568,"session":"a15401485","subject":"4URRL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29439,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12657,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f2"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23070,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":49012,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f4"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":69747,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10472,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22385,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43091,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f8"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20783,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0f9"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":52426,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0fa"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":116994,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0fb"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7776,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0fc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22668,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0fd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":25096,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef0fe"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28008,"session":"a16950015","subject":"8BB1M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef10a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":63218,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef10b"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7660,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef10c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9992,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef10d"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7208,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef10e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":10430,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef10f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6625,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef110"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24791,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef111"},"answer":"AGK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54595,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef112"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20214,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef113"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7330,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef114"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7793,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef115"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6399,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef116"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12302,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef117"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7753,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef118"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10841,"session":"a16613812","subject":"WRHPM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef124"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":54848,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef125"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12436,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef126"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":111589,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef127"},"answer":"UDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":38881,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef128"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":52277,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef129"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16439,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef12a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14839,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef12b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":38093,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef12c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22777,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef12d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8859,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef12e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":28887,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef12f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8240,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef130"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30525,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef131"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":38492,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef132"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41574,"session":"a16329216","subject":"77SKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef158"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":112274,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef159"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17060,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef15a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26327,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef15b"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10886,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef15c"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":33797,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef15d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13062,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef15e"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":93326,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef15f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":88421,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef160"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":129275,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef161"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":30008,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef162"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18124,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef163"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13720,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef164"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24845,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef165"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11658,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef166"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19969,"session":"a16906699","subject":"K7HM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef172"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":70405,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef173"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17916,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef174"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":52389,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef175"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20094,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef176"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32444,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef177"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14548,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef178"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36589,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef179"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":33547,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef17a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29564,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef17b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18264,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef17c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22572,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef17d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10914,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef17e"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18265,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef17f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15523,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef180"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21993,"session":"a15274291","subject":"EMKFA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef18c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44561,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef18d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18431,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef18e"},"answer":"AUB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":41380,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef18f"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16183,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef190"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":20084,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef191"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12456,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef192"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27449,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef193"},"answer":"L","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32569,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef194"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34154,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef195"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48038,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef196"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12135,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef197"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16729,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef198"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":95332,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef199"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39113,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef19a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47970,"session":"a16553672","subject":"S8NY4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1a6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":12557,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1a7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11330,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1a8"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18630,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1a9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10388,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1aa"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":3298,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1ab"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5938,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1ac"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20220,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1ad"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":21390,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1ae"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":1476,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1af"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2467,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1b0"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":1375,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1b1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":2987,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1b2"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":2712,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1b3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":3249,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1b4"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":3293,"session":"a15923414","subject":"YAFMA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19278,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23243,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c2"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":31457,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":76636,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c4"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":189458,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10111,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21292,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":31202,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c8"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":57564,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1c9"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":40611,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1ca"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":20507,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1cb"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":29481,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1cc"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":34630,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1cd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20639,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1ce"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":50864,"session":"a15558540\na15558540","subject":"PQA54"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1da"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26910,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1db"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10481,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1dc"},"answer":"AUB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":367447,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1dd"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":73607,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1de"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":76571,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1df"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5245,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17512,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":76118,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e2"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30253,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e3"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14573,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11787,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":42491,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e6"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":57384,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":69970,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":80269,"session":"a15957989","subject":"194UU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1f4"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":6256,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1f5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7642,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1f6"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15952,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1f7"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":41951,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1f8"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":84064,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1f9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10063,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1fa"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":9911,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1fb"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30222,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1fc"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":10831,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1fd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":3601,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1fe"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6647,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef1ff"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10095,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef200"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10206,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef201"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10420,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef202"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":67254,"session":"a16924586","subject":"802RA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef20e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25574,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef20f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19933,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef210"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26628,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef211"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":84657,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef212"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":119319,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef213"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13060,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef214"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35244,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef215"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49524,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef216"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26380,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef217"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":67391,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef218"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14544,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef219"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4091,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef21a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":34828,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef21b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33816,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef21c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":53814,"session":"a16675361\na16675361","subject":"FDRWD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef228"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7947,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef229"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9021,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef22a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13586,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef22b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20589,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef22c"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29478,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef22d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12235,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef22e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":7848,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef22f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":13883,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef230"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":11655,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef231"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7530,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef232"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6486,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef233"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11485,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef234"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9944,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef235"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":3238,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef236"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":90024,"session":"a16924586","subject":"XO4JG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef25c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18220,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef25d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10674,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef25e"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25393,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef25f"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":68052,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef260"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":196651,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef261"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8441,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef262"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24050,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef263"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":67739,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef264"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24252,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef265"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":67448,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef266"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12818,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef267"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6942,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef268"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":51456,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef269"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":51950,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef26a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":40486,"session":"a15867428","subject":"U820R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef276"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32952,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef277"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15203,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef278"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":35485,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef279"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":50001,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef27a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":66966,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef27b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12154,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef27c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":13388,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef27d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51575,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef27e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16096,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef27f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":42762,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef280"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10207,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef281"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7185,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef282"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":47086,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef283"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":37686,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef284"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46371,"session":"a15902241\na15902241","subject":"UH8DS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef290"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":49661,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef291"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12979,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef292"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":30164,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef293"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":40432,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef294"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":67892,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef295"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10206,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef296"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26966,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef297"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42776,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef298"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21525,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef299"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":56669,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef29a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12388,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef29b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9649,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef29c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33046,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef29d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":29301,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef29e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":30934,"session":"a15468160","subject":"UQTQ6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2aa"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":69582,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ab"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13845,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ac"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18448,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ad"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20653,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ae"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11915,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2af"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7968,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b0"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":40154,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b1"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73081,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b2"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":44120,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7841,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b4"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11358,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b5"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10731,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26447,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b7"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5506,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2b8"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10883,"session":"a15917800","subject":"PJYUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2c4"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":33011,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2c5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18376,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2c6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23194,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2c7"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26413,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2c8"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":55465,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2c9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11796,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ca"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16916,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2cb"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":33706,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2cc"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27354,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2cd"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":36801,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ce"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9508,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2cf"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8778,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2d0"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":42019,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2d1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":34128,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2d2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29354,"session":"a17126609","subject":"60VNG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2de"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19506,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2df"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24751,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e0"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":34317,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e1"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":42080,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e2"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":54768,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":26811,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":52411,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":103325,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e6"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24810,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":45098,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9837,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2e9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18538,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ea"},"answer":"LH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":57214,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2eb"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13442,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef2ec"},"answer":"EB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":99000,"session":"a17147364","subject":"EA6YH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef312"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15705,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef313"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6887,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef314"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13719,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef315"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":57065,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef316"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":45308,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef317"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6267,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef318"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19585,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef319"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54053,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef31a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40376,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef31b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23760,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef31c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":23268,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef31d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7296,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef31e"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":34951,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef31f"},"answer":"BX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":36990,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef320"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":60088,"session":"a16965466","subject":"UO0XA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef32c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36933,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef32d"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":36768,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef32e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28888,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef32f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":36809,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef330"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":56859,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef331"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14142,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef332"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20992,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef333"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":27049,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef334"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14449,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef335"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":34986,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef336"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8588,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef337"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12642,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef338"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27917,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef339"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":80911,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef33a"},"answer":"N","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":3894,"session":"a16247152","subject":"6VLV8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef346"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37427,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef347"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9305,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef348"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13842,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef349"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7075,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef34a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24347,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef34b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6086,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef34c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15120,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef34d"},"answer":"FGC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":18486,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef34e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21282,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef34f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14742,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef350"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5885,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef351"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4059,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef352"},"answer":"ND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17056,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef353"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10574,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef354"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":7385,"session":"a15428681","subject":"KPZTN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef360"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40306,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef361"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9805,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef362"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16057,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef363"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7991,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef364"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":26364,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef365"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14820,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef366"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24778,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef367"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":56379,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef368"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29652,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef369"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8036,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef36a"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13810,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef36b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8783,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef36c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12972,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef36d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13256,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef36e"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13413,"session":"a16788617\na16788617","subject":"W8QQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef37a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22101,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef37b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11024,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef37c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13937,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef37d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":84238,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef37e"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":74202,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef37f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9233,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef380"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29318,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef381"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46158,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef382"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29232,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef383"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9492,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef384"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8678,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef385"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11836,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef386"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":34845,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef387"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":175719,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef388"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":31810,"session":"a15513832","subject":"7BV0L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef394"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29374,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef395"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21900,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef396"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19298,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef397"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8816,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef398"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":19156,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef399"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20624,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef39a"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":33051,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef39b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46655,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef39c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27434,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef39d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":32441,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef39e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9277,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef39f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13288,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3a0"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23485,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3a1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10722,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3a2"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21528,"session":"a15897677\na15897677","subject":"K5PDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ae"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":13189,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3af"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7305,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b0"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":39290,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b1"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":45679,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b2"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":52410,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6856,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b4"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15031,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b5"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28183,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13220,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10476,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9618,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3b9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3427,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ba"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":43063,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3bb"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12842,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3bc"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20103,"session":"a15454598","subject":"GB4TH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3c8"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":14227,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3c9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11496,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ca"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12157,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3cb"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12013,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3cc"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29618,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3cd"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6874,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ce"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30509,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3cf"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":56461,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":33557,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d1"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":40761,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7483,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9657,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d4"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":38898,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":35730,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3d6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":52607,"session":"a15992680","subject":"X8P7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e2"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21534,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e3"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16186,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e4"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7608,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8462,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e6"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":14485,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10176,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e8"},"answer":"CH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19731,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3e9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":6090,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ea"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13904,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3eb"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14084,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ec"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13409,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ed"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5446,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ee"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23244,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3ef"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7963,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef3f0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":4140,"session":"a1770579","subject":"DGJQ3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef416"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":52560,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef417"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11126,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef418"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12293,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef419"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":53924,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef41a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":43912,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef41b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8225,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef41c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15861,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef41d"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":69383,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef41e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16522,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef41f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":25179,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef420"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11542,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef421"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9483,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef422"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29735,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef423"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20542,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef424"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":126591,"session":"a15585339","subject":"WUB39"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef430"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":138925,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef431"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14767,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef432"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":118254,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef433"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15110,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef434"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13364,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef435"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":33582,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef436"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":48353,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef437"},"answer":"GC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":92611,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef438"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":42069,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef439"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21224,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef43a"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12578,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef43b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13331,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef43c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13616,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef43d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8048,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef43e"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11763,"session":"a16137762","subject":"N34B6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef44a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":273493,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef44b"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16104,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef44c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":77184,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef44d"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":52003,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef44e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24343,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef44f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13477,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef450"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":53318,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef451"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":79872,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef452"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":60367,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef453"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":88167,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef454"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":47818,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef455"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":53688,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef456"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26608,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef457"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20236,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef458"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29652,"session":"a16775456","subject":"02DBM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef464"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40599,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef465"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6730,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef466"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24724,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef467"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10267,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef468"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36232,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef469"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22145,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef46a"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21499,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef46b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29447,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef46c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":102988,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef46d"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5966,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef46e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8187,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef46f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef470"},"answer":"ZN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11298,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef471"},"answer":"P","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9963,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef472"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12394,"session":"a15839424","subject":"7DJGJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef498"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29627,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef499"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16185,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef49a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":33683,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef49b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":127676,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef49c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":63714,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef49d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13748,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef49e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":199396,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef49f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":41341,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":60053,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":152617,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":131262,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":23848,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":41332,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23693,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4a6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41599,"session":"a16681470","subject":"2CZP7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b2"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32685,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10854,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23900,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":4,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":103732,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11048,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":67805,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4b9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34408,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4ba"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17163,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4bb"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":61431,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4bc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8998,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4bd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8070,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4be"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":39193,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4bf"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":37714,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4c0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":34919,"session":"a15927876","subject":"YJN2B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4cc"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":10530,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4cd"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30235,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4ce"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23670,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4cf"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":38835,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":41148,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20683,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d2"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":103352,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d3"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":158450,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":89257,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":89577,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18074,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":69487,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d8"},"answer":"ND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":89092,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4d9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16700,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4da"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":71897,"session":"a17082219\na17082219","subject":"ELVPK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4e6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":4836,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4e7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11345,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4e8"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8759,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4e9"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26303,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4ea"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":61103,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4eb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5916,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4ec"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":10126,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4ed"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":22684,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4ee"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":10779,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4ef"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22280,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4f0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5318,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4f1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7578,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4f2"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19577,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4f3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13194,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef4f4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16473,"session":"a16664786","subject":"VRHYF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef51a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27273,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef51b"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":250218,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef51c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":106845,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef51d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":73797,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef51e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":289179,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef51f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8409,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef520"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":41031,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef521"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":142862,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef522"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":73137,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef523"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48949,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef524"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21652,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef525"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9797,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef526"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":126155,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef527"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":162256,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef528"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":74222,"session":"a15853813","subject":"694WT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef534"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":204844,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef535"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9039,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef536"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":34132,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef537"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10237,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef538"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":111530,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef539"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10153,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef53a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19671,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef53b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":94031,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef53c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15028,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef53d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21614,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef53e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9746,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef53f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":75901,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef540"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19523,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef541"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":82070,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef542"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24423,"session":"a17091192\na17091192","subject":"QADB9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef54e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23744,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef54f"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16146,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef550"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18676,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef551"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":36493,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef552"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":41398,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef553"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9744,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef554"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17223,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef555"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25219,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef556"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22653,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef557"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8103,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef558"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5762,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef559"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6155,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef55a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":66385,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef55b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33305,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef55c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":45977,"session":"a16137081\na16137081","subject":"PRA08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef59c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":12459,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef59d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14340,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef59e"},"answer":"AIOZFHJXKUDEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":16.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":64017,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef59f"},"answer":"CAIOZFHJXKU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":13.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":69177,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a0"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":49605,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":40838,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30824,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":65800,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":32389,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":74592,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15932,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13571,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":69618,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5a9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":43379,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5aa"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":87451,"session":"a15545916","subject":"KXRFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5b6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20672,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5b7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10324,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5b8"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15244,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5b9"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":68592,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5ba"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":98198,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5bb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6982,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5bc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16072,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5bd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32241,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5be"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20539,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5bf"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":49399,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5c0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8463,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5c1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5640,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5c2"},"answer":"BX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18179,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5c3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42581,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5c4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28240,"session":"a16194024","subject":"LPY8N"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":8526,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d1"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6296,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d2"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9371,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d3"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15732,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d4"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118073,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9504,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d6"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24553,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d7"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25167,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d8"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37472,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5d9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11429,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5da"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6892,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5db"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6939,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5dc"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12257,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5dd"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7166,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5de"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":105296,"session":"a16430000","subject":"5P3XF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5ea"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22305,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5eb"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11218,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5ec"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20454,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5ed"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":56284,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5ee"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":49189,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5ef"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5917,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16476,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37848,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f2"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17024,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f3"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":35266,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15052,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6700,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f6"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16481,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20980,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef5f8"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":39816,"session":"a15874333","subject":"AU0MW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef604"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":71604,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef605"},"answer":"GB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":29164,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef606"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":306860,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef607"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":24063,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef608"},"answer":"ZXU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":8265,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef609"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9583,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef60a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23552,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef60b"},"answer":"L","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24014,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef60c"},"answer":"AGN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":4346,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef60d"},"answer":"MAX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7545,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef60e"},"answer":"BH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":3112,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef60f"},"answer":"BZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3454,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef610"},"answer":"EC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":5052,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef611"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":4157,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef612"},"answer":"AKXP","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9544,"session":"a15926963","subject":"HCGNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef61e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32404,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef61f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12403,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef620"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18298,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef621"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":48273,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef622"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":90977,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef623"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7628,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef624"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16137,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef625"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29031,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef626"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30463,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef627"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28276,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef628"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11801,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef629"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5435,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef62a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17207,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef62b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":41568,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef62c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36316,"session":"a15530049","subject":"STJP3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef638"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18237,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef639"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12252,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef63a"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":34073,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef63b"},"answer":"KU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":14091,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef63c"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":340486,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef63d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8248,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef63e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20980,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef63f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46179,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef640"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":44400,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef641"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17099,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef642"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12596,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef643"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7247,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef644"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29482,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef645"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22448,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef646"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":39667,"session":"a15461338","subject":"GY85V"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef652"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31010,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef653"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14136,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef654"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":80910,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef655"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":60644,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef656"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":193304,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef657"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10800,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef658"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":93822,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef659"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":91236,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef65a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":46427,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef65b"},"answer":"P","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":27951,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef65c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13639,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef65d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18954,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef65e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":82152,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef65f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":102332,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef660"},"answer":"EFB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":142898,"session":"a16546781","subject":"3PADQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef66c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":41140,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef66d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13129,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef66e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12118,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef66f"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13618,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef670"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":19820,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef671"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7714,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef672"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27240,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef673"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55383,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef674"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27985,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef675"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5856,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef676"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9200,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef677"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":26254,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef678"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":46670,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef679"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18574,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef67a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29737,"session":"a15903042","subject":"240Y4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef686"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":35344,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef687"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14801,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef688"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10936,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef689"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10845,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef68a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13684,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef68b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9302,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef68c"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":38990,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef68d"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":71128,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef68e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31189,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef68f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12378,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef690"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14284,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef691"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7164,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef692"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13459,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef693"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8512,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef694"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12949,"session":"a15568892","subject":"3SYRX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6d4"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":35324,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6d5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22609,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6d6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18736,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6d7"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":140712,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6d8"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":101336,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6d9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22480,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6da"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20306,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6db"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":116303,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6dc"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26998,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6dd"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":38759,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6de"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15509,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6df"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13526,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6e0"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":55226,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6e1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":119884,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef6e2"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":59076,"session":"a16145321","subject":"PFFEV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef708"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":146880,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef709"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19389,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef70a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12730,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef70b"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18337,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef70c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27607,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef70d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":61811,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef70e"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":33467,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef70f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44657,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef710"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":52175,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef711"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11377,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef712"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17273,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef713"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8615,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef714"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13797,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef715"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10869,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef716"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24373,"session":"a15386946","subject":"NH0FO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef722"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":8605,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef723"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15686,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef724"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":31201,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef725"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58505,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef726"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":78490,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef727"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8132,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef728"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26791,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef729"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43824,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef72a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":28640,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef72b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6691,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef72c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14710,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef72d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8215,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef72e"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":52030,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef72f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8476,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef730"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":63181,"session":"a15865479","subject":"XG38D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef73c"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37988,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef73d"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":71552,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef73e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11236,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef73f"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26095,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef740"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":47770,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef741"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8891,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef742"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18975,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef743"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":66504,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef744"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":47033,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef745"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":134616,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef746"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12127,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef747"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6717,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef748"},"answer":"ACX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50561,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef749"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39796,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef74a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46579,"session":"a16041987","subject":"N36VM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef756"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7257,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef757"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12399,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef758"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12398,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef759"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7661,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef75a"},"answer":"HJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11208,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef75b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6427,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef75c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15368,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef75d"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":6685,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef75e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":6116,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef75f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16032,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef760"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9682,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef761"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5054,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef762"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12976,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef763"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8578,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef764"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18739,"session":"a16677006","subject":"7METL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef78a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":64180,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef78b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7833,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef78c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11932,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef78d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":42715,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef78e"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":42801,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef78f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8848,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef790"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":134256,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef791"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24673,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef792"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15816,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef793"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16227,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef794"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8999,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef795"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3920,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef796"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17540,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef797"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11357,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef798"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":8555,"session":"a15826500\na15826500\na15826500","subject":"XV7KZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7a4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15855,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7a5"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8062,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7a6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19794,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7a7"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8070,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7a8"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":51562,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7a9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10804,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7aa"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19013,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7ab"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40549,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7ac"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":62561,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7ad"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6853,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7ae"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12366,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7af"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9816,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7b0"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14178,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7b1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7772,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7b2"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":57909,"session":"a15049392\na15049392","subject":"BASO5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7d8"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37027,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7d9"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13757,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7da"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":36650,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7db"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":42321,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7dc"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":83842,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7dd"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":77176,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7de"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":55100,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":67354,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":56180,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10093,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e2"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13323,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10311,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":36546,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10919,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7e6"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":130423,"session":"a16578015","subject":"YUWCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f2"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19992,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f3"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19514,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f4"},"answer":"KD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14301,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f5"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":62863,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27203,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6515,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f8"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18801,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7f9"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":11.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":125115,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7fa"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24110,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7fb"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9027,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7fc"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13266,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7fd"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8115,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7fe"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10603,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef7ff"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11427,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef800"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11358,"session":"a16806645","subject":"CN995"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef80c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":34264,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef80d"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22723,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef80e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15738,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef80f"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11178,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef810"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":22122,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef811"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12365,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef812"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":41083,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef813"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":65962,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef814"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":81949,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef815"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8890,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef816"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10795,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef817"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9015,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef818"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":42578,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef819"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6654,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef81a"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17538,"session":"a16148682","subject":"98R7E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef826"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17762,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef827"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8757,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef828"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22011,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef829"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":84550,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef82a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":34508,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef82b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8463,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef82c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21656,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef82d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29064,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef82e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":131495,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef82f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17033,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef830"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12775,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef831"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":34987,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef832"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":40107,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef833"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":36382,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef834"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":225982,"session":"a16686690\n16686690\n16686690","subject":"ZZNSP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef840"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":360629,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef841"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":27180,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef842"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12632,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef843"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15312,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef844"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":64258,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef845"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6733,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef846"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16162,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef847"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73984,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef848"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26045,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef849"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":85109,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef84a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17642,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef84b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8823,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef84c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29671,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef84d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23029,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef84e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":61659,"session":"a15585339","subject":"77W0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef85a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25508,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef85b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19941,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef85c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":6820,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef85d"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":94926,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef85e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24851,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef85f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22558,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef860"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17754,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef861"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54216,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef862"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31889,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef863"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":27428,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef864"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8812,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef865"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6234,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef866"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28350,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef867"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":26726,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef868"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":42149,"session":"a16144697","subject":"PY424"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef874"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":85281,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef875"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12322,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef876"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":52085,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef877"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8162,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef878"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":17371,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef879"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7647,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef87a"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":47224,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef87b"},"answer":"IJEFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47727,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef87c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":92097,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef87d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11949,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef87e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10668,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef87f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8929,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef880"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16265,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef881"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12881,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef882"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12613,"session":"a15526867","subject":"N5NRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef88e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":74267,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef88f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24635,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef890"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17323,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef891"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":21512,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef892"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27282,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef893"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16474,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef894"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":45635,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef895"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":125686,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef896"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":70113,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef897"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19762,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef898"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15016,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef899"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13976,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef89a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28238,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef89b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11064,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef89c"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33337,"session":"a16263989","subject":"QXNXR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8a8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":52894,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8a9"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10912,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8aa"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11916,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ab"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10994,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ac"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13307,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ad"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":46297,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ae"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28496,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8af"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":136302,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b0"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":51347,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16285,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b2"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12710,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9960,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b4"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11254,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7551,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8b6"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17261,"session":"a16648429","subject":"MAJW8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c2"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19741,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14990,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c4"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12506,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c5"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20355,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c6"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27605,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":72610,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c8"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15176,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8c9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":212910,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ca"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":71070,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8cb"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":82074,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8cc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15293,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8cd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5763,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ce"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26332,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8cf"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":49549,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8d0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29174,"session":"a6125989","subject":"DMUWM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8dc"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":49632,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8dd"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":59998,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8de"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13404,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8df"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8538,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":67755,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9555,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e2"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":45548,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":64397,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":45954,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7948,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e6"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6097,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8798,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e8"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11599,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8e9"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6907,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ea"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17636,"session":"a15480541","subject":"Y9SMP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8f6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":62578,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8f7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21828,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8f8"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":53361,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8f9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":27725,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8fa"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13317,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8fb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":28275,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8fc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27307,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8fd"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":53880,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8fe"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":9053,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef8ff"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":33248,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef900"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8324,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef901"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12578,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef902"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25417,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef903"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":110789,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef904"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13809,"session":"w17156565","subject":"SG6TQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef910"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":8908,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef911"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":139128,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef912"},"answer":"OK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":169615,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef913"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13363,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef914"},"answer":"DG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":73394,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef915"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9355,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef916"},"answer":"MO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":123021,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef917"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":70221,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef918"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30097,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef919"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18067,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef91a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":36358,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef91b"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":86134,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef91c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27903,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef91d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":134273,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef91e"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":34210,"session":"a16759561","subject":"1JW7Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef92a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":63180,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef92b"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":40959,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef92c"},"answer":"ZFJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":49758,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef92d"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":78706,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef92e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":248798,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef92f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7846,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef930"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16607,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef931"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37432,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef932"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39149,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef933"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":30461,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef934"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6940,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef935"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6612,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef936"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":42536,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef937"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":40464,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef938"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46711,"session":"a15399879","subject":"ARL8H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef944"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":59830,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef945"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17662,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef946"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12161,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef947"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9645,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef948"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21162,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef949"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":53348,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef94a"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16537,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef94b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47888,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef94c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26902,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef94d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9142,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef94e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9142,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef94f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9809,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef950"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12392,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef951"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5704,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef952"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9255,"session":"a15904376","subject":"1KLRO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef95e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":64563,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef95f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22683,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef960"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13247,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef961"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20950,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef962"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":72325,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef963"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16701,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef964"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":44138,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef965"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47237,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef966"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29456,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef967"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11949,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef968"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15973,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef969"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16912,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef96a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":39388,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef96b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9642,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef96c"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15973,"session":"a16143560","subject":"WZMMU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef978"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24010,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef979"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":44067,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef97a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10415,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef97b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":65387,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef97c"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":107023,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef97d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9473,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef97e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":13270,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef97f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":52420,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef980"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16466,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef981"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":218599,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef982"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":38568,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef983"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7497,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef984"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32837,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef985"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":40245,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef986"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":92233,"session":"a15767120","subject":"M9WY5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef992"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":68586,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef993"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16622,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef994"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14227,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef995"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":14397,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef996"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":72775,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef997"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22727,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef998"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":44439,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef999"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":68126,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef99a"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24122,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef99b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12238,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef99c"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12661,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef99d"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14754,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef99e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":38354,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef99f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11250,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9a0"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41795,"session":"a17129477","subject":"SQKR9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9ac"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":96400,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9ad"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":33005,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9ae"},"answer":"FHJKUDEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":11,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":73091,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9af"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":235981,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b0"},"answer":"OJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":339354,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11497,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":72432,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b3"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":250184,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":122410,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":127094,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8607,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5757,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21643,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9b9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":41468,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9ba"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28699,"session":"a15920946","subject":"N8PCJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9c6"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28884,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9c7"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8637,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9c8"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16997,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9c9"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":59857,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9ca"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29897,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9cb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7205,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9cc"},"answer":"IJFBXOZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":9,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":43724,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9cd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40019,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9ce"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13850,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9cf"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23617,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9d0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11377,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9d1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7888,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9d2"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22896,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9d3"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18461,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61f34674f32bcfe23f6ef9d4"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":22996,"session":"a17169808","subject":"M53XH"}]
